Guide to the Hudson Guild records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Hudson Guild Files
  - Subseries III.1: Alphabetical Subjects
    Includes administrative memos, annual reports, constitution and by-laws, publicity materials, membership lists, news clippings, promotional materials, publications, staff manuals
    - Alumni, 1945-1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Alumni--John Blatt, ca. 1990 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Anniversaries:
      - 45th, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - 50th, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - 75th, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - 100th, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Appeals, 1930-1955 (Box 13, Folder 7-9)
    - Audit Report, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Bank Resolutions, 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Benefits, 1954-1972 nd (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Book Fair, 1960, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Budgets, 1945-1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Building:
      - Edelbaum and Webster, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - General, 1964-1970 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Lanning Mural, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Maps and Plans, 1962-1965 [nd] (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Building Fund, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1897, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Committee to Consider the Minority Groups Male's Self-Image, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Community Involvement, 1969-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Community Problems:
      - Bayview, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Housing, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - 26th Street Incident, 1964-1974 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - 27th Street, 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, 1946-1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Dance Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Employment Practices, 1946-1966 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Fall Conference:
      - 1945 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - 1962-1974 (Box 36, Folder 32-37)
      - 1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Fund Raising, 1945-1947 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Histories, 1938-1993 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - House Rules, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Hudson Guild and Neighborhood Directories, 1969-1975 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Integration, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Job Descriptions, 1970s-1980s (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Junto Club, 1900-191920 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Mailing Lists, nd (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Membership List, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Neighborhood Advisory Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - News Clippings:
      - Photocopies, 1926-1959 (Box 37, Folder 49-50)
      - Photocopies, 1960-1979 (Box 14, Folder 51-52)
      - Photocopies, 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 53)
      - Originals, 1926-1988 (Box 45, Folder 54-58)
    - Old Timers, 1935-1940 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Organization Charts, 1948-1972 nd (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Policy Statements, 1948-1989 nd (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Proclamations, 1985-1988 (Box 45, Folder 62)
    - Promotional Material, ca. 1930-1949 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Promotional Material, 1950-1967 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Promotional Material, 1970-1973 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Publicity, 1952-1975 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Reorganization Plan, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Spring Festival, 1965-1978 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Staff Administrative Responsibilities, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Staff Directory, 1972 [nd] (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Staff Manual, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Staff Manual, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Staff Members--Edd Lee, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Staff Members -Ross, 1924-1945 (Box 37, Folder 74-75)
    - Statistics, 1951-1975 (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - Sustaining Fund, 1934, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Volunteer Department, 1952-1969 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Volunteer Department, 1970-1973 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - Subseries III.2: Hudson Guild Council
    Includes committee files, memos, minutes and Membership.
    - By-Laws, 1965-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Dissident Groups--Black Arts, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Dissident Groups--Young Adults, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Education, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Education, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - General, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - House Rules Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Membership, 1968-1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Minutes:
      - 1960-1970 (Box 16, Folder 10-16)
      - 1971-1976 (Box 17, Folder 17-22)
  - Subseries III.3: Publications
    Includes annual and special reports, directories and periodicals published under Hudson Guild auspices.
    - Alumni News, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1910-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2-7)
    - "Building the New Chelsea," ca. 1961 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - "Capital Expansion Needs," 1951 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Directory of Social Services and Neighborhood Organizations in Chelsea," 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Hudson Guild Calendar, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Hudson Guild News, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hudson Guild Report, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "Living in Chelsea," 1954 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - News from the Hudson Guild, 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 16-18)
    - Newsletter, 1965-1972 (Box 19, Folder 19-23)
    - People's Voice, ca. 1938 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "Some Pertinent Facts About a Housing Cooperative," 1958 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Souvenir Journal, 1962-1969 (Box 19, Folder 26-28)
    - Hudson Guild Today (Winter 1997) (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Series IV: Programs
  - Subseries IV.1: Alphabetical File
    Includes correspondence, memos, reports, statistical and narrative reports, news clippings, proposals, flyers and announcements. Folder 11 contains confidential case notes and is closed to researchers until 2030.
    - Art Gallery, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Basic English Project, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Camp Madison-Felicia, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Cellar Players, 1923-1929 [nd] (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Chelsea Closed Circuit Television Project, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    - Chelsea Housing and Human Relations Project, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Child Care Center, 1947-1951 [nd] (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Children's Programs, 1937-1939 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Cooperative Nursery School, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Counseling Service:
      - Case Notes, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 11)
        [restricted until 2030]
      - French and Polyclinic Affiliation, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - General, 1951-1965 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - General, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - General, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Marginal Youth, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Study, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Therapeutic Nursery Group, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Day Camp, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Day Care--Union Matters, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Day Care--Union Matters, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Day Care--Union Matters, 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Dramatics, 1927 [nd] (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Drop-Out Prevention, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Education Center:
      - Study Den, 1957, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 26-27)
      - Study Den, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Study Den--Annual Report, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Evening Pottery, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Family Life Management, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Group Work Department, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Head Start, 1967-1985 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Homeless Projects, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Housing for the Elderly, 1961-1972 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Housing for the Elderly, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Hudson Guild Cooks, nd (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Juvenile Delinquency, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Library--Accession Book, 1930-1941 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Flyers, nd (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Mothers' Club, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Neighborhood Conservation, 1953-1959 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Neighborhood Prevention Network, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - New California Hotel Project, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - New Neighbors, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Program Areas Outline, 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Program Guide, ca. 1967 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Proposals, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - School Age Center, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - School for Printers' Apprentices, 1913-1915 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Take Back the Park, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Teenage Opportunity Program, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Subseries IV.2: Fulton Senior Citizens' Center
    Includes correspondence, memos, reports, statistical and narrative reports, news clippings, proposals, flyers and announcements.
    - C.A.F.E. Co-op, 1966-1970 (Box 23, Folder 1-1)
    - C.A.F.E. Co-op, 1971-1974 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Communicator Project, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Communicator Project, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Communicator Project, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Communicator Project, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Department of Welfare, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Despres Conference, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Evaluation, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Fulton Chronicle, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
    - Fulton Senior Association, 1966-1975 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The Fulton Senior Voice, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Health Maintenance Clinic, 1961-1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Opening, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Survey, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Title III, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Title VI, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Title XVI, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Title XVI, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Title XVI, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Title XX, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Subseries IV.3: Hudson Guild Farm
    - Assessment, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - Despres Cottage, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - General, 1918-1985 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Hecht Correspondence, 1957-1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Histories, 1947 nd (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Maps and Plans, 1922-1965 nd (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Rates, 1970-1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Reports, 1920-1939 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Reports, 1948-1962 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Reports, 1963-1968 nd (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Subseries IV.4: Hudson Guild Theater
    - Awards, 1976-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Ground Plan, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Playbill, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Programs, ca. 1905 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Promotional Material, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Proposals, 1968 nd (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Publicity Scrapbooks:
      - 1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - 1983-1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Script, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Showbill, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
- Series V: Scrapbooks
  Chronologically compiled scrapbooks contain correspondence and memos, news clippings, photographs, program fliers and announcements.
  - Publicity, 1940-1952 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Elliott Houses, 1946-1947 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Letters and Brochures, 1950s-1970s (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1952-1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings:
    - Originals, 1959-1965 (Box 28, Folder 5-7)
    - Photocopies, 1959-1965 (Box 29, Folder 8-10)
  - Cooking, Sewing, Bingo, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Dedication of Solomon Cottage, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Hudson Guild Farm, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Kindergarten, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Youth Programs, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Photographs
  Black and white and color photoprints, negatives and transparencies. Subjects include settlement staff and program participants, neighborhood scenes, settlement buildings, and camp.
  - Adults:
    - Art and Cultural Activities, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25000-25008)
    - Groups Portraits, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25009-25028)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25029-25050)
    - Portraits, 1920s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25051-25058)
  - After School Program, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25059-25063)
  - Art Gallery:
    - Artwork Close-ups, ca. 1975 (Box 30, Folder 25064-25088)
    - Shows, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 25089-25093)
    - Shows, ca. 1975 (Box 30, Folder 25094-25111)
    - Shows, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 25112-25123)
    - Shows, ca. 1970-1985 (Box 30, Folder 25124-25138)
    - Shows, ca. 1970-1985 (Box 30, Folder 25139-25153)
  - Athletics:
    - Awards, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 25154-25168)
    - Awards, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25169-25185)
    - Basketball, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25186-25200)
    - Basketball, 1960s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25201-25213)
    - Boxing, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25214-25219)
  - Athletics:
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25220-25233)
    - Miscellaneous. 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25234-25248)
    - Milton Avery Visit, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 25249-25250)
  - Award Ceremonies. 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25251-25267)
  - Bazaars, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25268-25290)
  - Benefits, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25291-25292)
  - Board Members, 1920s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25293-25296)
  - Book Fairs, 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 25297-25307)
  - Boys' Club Meeting, ca. 1910 (Box 30, Folder 25308)
  - Bus Trips, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25309-25314)
  - Camp Madison-Felicia, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 25315-25329)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25330-25341)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1920s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25342-25354)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1920s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25355-25363)
  - Centennial Exhibit, ca. 1910-80s (Box 30, Folder 24364-25375)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1930s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25376-25387)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1890s-191970s (Box 30, Folder 25388-25407)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1920s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25408-25428)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25429-25442)
  - Centennial Exhibit, ca. 1910-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25443-25459)
  - Centennial Exhibit, 1910s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25460-25468)
  - Chelsea Closed Circuit Television, ca. 1960 (Box 30, Folder 25469)
  - Chelsea Defense Council, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 25470)
  - Chelsea Park, ca. 1915 (Box 30, Folder 25471-25505)
  - Chelsea Park Movies, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 25506)
  - Chelsea Revitalization Plan, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 25507-25518)
  - Chelsea Street Scenes, ca. 1920-1950s (Box 30, Folder 25519-25538)
  - Chelsea Street Scenes, 1950s-60s (Box 30, Folder 25539-25557)
  - Chelsea Street Scenes, 1950s-60s (Box 30, Folder 25558-25579)
  - Church Interiors, nd (Box 30, Folder 25580-25581)
  - Children:
    - Arts and Crafts, 1 9405-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25582-25608)
    - Cooking and Eating, 1920s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25609-25628)
    - Cooking and Eating, 1 9205-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25629-25647)
    - Cooking and Eating, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25648-25662)
    - Cooking and Eating, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25663-25677)
    - In Gymnasium, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25678-25697)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25698-25712)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25713-25732)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25733-25755)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25756-25774)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25775-25795)
    - Music and Drama, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25796-25819)
    - Naps, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25820-25829)
    - On Roof, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 25830-25834)
    - Outdoors, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25835-25859)
    - Outdoors, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 25860-25879)
    - Parties, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25880-25892)
    - Performances, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25893-25917)
    - Reading, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25918-25946)
    - Telephone Company Visit, ca. 1970 (Box 30, Folder 25947-25954)
  - Christmas, 1930s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 25955-25974)
  - Dances, ca. 1950 (Box 30, Folder 25975-25977)
  - Day Care -Morning Walk, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 25978)
  - Despres Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 25979-25981)
  - Earth Day, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 25982)
  - Dinners, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 25983-25998)
  - Dinners, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 25999-26003)
  - Dramatics, 1920s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 26003-26030)
  - Education Center, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 26031)
  - John Lovejoy Elliott, nd (Box 30, Folder 26032-26038)
  - Elliott-Chelsea Nautical Cadets, nd (Box 30, Folder 26039)
  - Elliott Dinners, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26040-26062)
  - El Rey Club, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 26063)
  - English Classes, 1929-1950 (Box 30, Folder 26064-26080)
  - Exhibits, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 26081-26086)
  - Fall Conference, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 26087)
  - Family Portrait, ca. 1910 (Box 30, Folder 26088)
  - Famous Visitors, 1940s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26089-26096)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 26097-26102)
  - William Gowrie DiInner, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 26103-26105)
  - Greater New York Fund Visit, ca. 1968 (Box 30, Folder 26106-26123)
  - Halloween, 1944-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26124-26129)
  - Health Care, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 26130-26135)
  - Hudson Guild Buildings, 1940-1968 (Box 30, Folder 26136-26150)
  - Hudson Guild Building Ceremonies, 1960-1968 (Box 30, Folder 26151-26158)
  - Hudson Guild Council, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 26159)
  - Hudson Guild Farm:
    - Animals, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26160-26168)
    - Buildings, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26169-26192)
    - Building Dedications, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 26193-26207)
    - Children and Teens, 1920s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26208-26234)
    - Conferences, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26235-26253)
    - Conferences, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26254-26277)
    - Conference--Outdoor Meetings, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26278-26293)
    - Dances 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 26294-26296)
    - Exhibit, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 26297-26301)
    - Exhibit, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 26302-26307)
    - Exhibit, ca. 1920-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26308-26312)
    - Exhibit, ca. 1920-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26313-26316)
    - Garden, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 26317-26319)
    - Landscapes, 1920s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26320-26328)
    - Meals, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26329-26336)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26337-26355)
    - Senior Citizens, 1 9605-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26356-26371)
    - Staff, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26372-26375)
    - Swimming and Boating, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26376-26397)
    - Winter, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26398-26415)
  - Hudson Guild Theater, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26416-26437)
  - Hudson Guild Theater, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26438-26459)
  - Hudson Guild Theater Performer Portraits, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26460-26480)
  - Job Orientation at Con Edison, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 26481-26499)
  - John Kennedy, nd (Box 30, Folder 26500)
  - Lanning Mural, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 26501-26505)
  - R. Edward Lee, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 26506-26511)
  - Mayor Lindsay Visit, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 26512-26518)
  - McGraw Awards. 1971-1981 (Box 30, Folder 26519-26533)
  - McGraw Awards, 1971-1981 (Box 30, Folder 26534-26553)
  - Meetings, 1 9505-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26554-26576)
  - Meetings, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26577-26598)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26599-26615)
  - Model Apartment Furniture, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 26616-26641)
  - Mothers' Club, 1930s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 26642-26646)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 26647-26648)
  - New York Knicks Visit, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 26649)
  - Nursery--Head Start Parents Meeting, ca. 1970 (Box 30, Folder 26650)
  - Nursery School Move, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 26651-26657)
  - Otis Graduate Trainees, ca. 1970 (Box 30, Folder 26658-26674)
  - Parents and Wives Club Dinner, ca.1950 (Box 30, Folder 26675-26684)
  - Parties, 1940s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26685-26719)
  - Poetry Readings, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 26720-26747)
  - Ronald Reagan Visit, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 26748-26758)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Visit, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 26759-26763)
  - School for Printers' Apprentices, ca. 1910 (Box 30, Folder 26764-26770)
  - School for Printers' Apprentices, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 26771-26788)
  - Shoemaking Class, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 26789)
  - S.HAR.E. Program, ca. 1970 (Box 30, Folder 26790-26791)
  - Senior Citizens:
    - Art and Cultural Activities, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26792-26815)
    - Art and Cultural Activities, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26816-26838)
    - Cooking Demonstration, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 26839-26847)
    - Dinner with Dan Carpenter, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 26848-26859)
    - Dinners and Parties, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26860-26881)
    - Fulton Center, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 26882-26895)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 26896-26920)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26921-26940)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 26941-26960)
  - Servicemen, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 26961-26992)
  - Sewing Class. ca. 1970 (Box 30, Folder 26993-26997)
  - Sexuality and Growing Up Community Meeting, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 26998)
  - Spring Festival, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 26999)
  - Street Lighting Improvement Committee, ca. 1950 (Box 30, Folder 27000)
  - Study Den, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 27001-27012)
  - Summer Pushcart Program, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 27013)
  - Teens:
    - Art and Cultural Activities, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 27014-27039)
    - Dances, 1940s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 27040-27047)
    - Educational Programs, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 27048-27055)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 27056-27058)
    - Work Projects, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 27086-27098)
  - Tenant Meetings, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 27099-27108)
  - Typing Class, ca. 1970 (Box 30, Folder 27109)
  - Veterans' Dinner, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 27100-27113)
  - Volunteers, 1950s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 27114-27134)
  - Robert Wagner Visit, 1960s (Box 30, Folder 27135-27138)
  - Wood Shop, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 27139-27164)
  - Oversize prints:
    - Children, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 27165-27171)
    - Woodshop. ca. 1950 (Box 30, Folder 27172-27173)
    - Kindergarten, ca. 1920 (Box 30, Folder 27174)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Meeting, ca. 1940 (Box 30, Folder 27175-27176)
    - Movies in Chelsea Park, ca. 1915 (Box 30, Folder 27177)
    - Library, ca. 1910 (Box 30, Folder 27178)
    - Senior Citizens, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 27179-27188)
    - Hudson Guild Theater. 1980s (Box 30, Folder 27189-27195)
    - Miscellaneous, ca. 1910-1980 (Box 30, Folder 27196-27206)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Meetings, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 27207-27254)
    - Children, ca. 1920 (Box 30, Folder 27255)
    - Mothers' Club George Washington Party, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 27256)
    - Junto Club Banquet, 1914 (Box 30, Folder 27257)
    - Fifth Annual Dinner, League of Mothers' Clubs of United Neighborhood Houses, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 27258)
    - 25th Anniversary Dinner, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 27259)
    - 30th Anniversary Dinner, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 27260)
    - 5th Annual ball, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 27261)
    - Movies in Chelsea Park, ca. 1915 (Box 30, Folder 27262)
    - Hudson Guild Farm--Labor Day, ca. 1920 (Box 30, Folder 27263)
    - John Lovejoy Elliott, nd (Box 30, Folder 27264)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Spring Reunion Exhibit, ca. 1920-1928 [In Mapcase 14-L-1] (Box 30, Folder 27265-27281)
  - Water Damaged Prints:
    - Unidentified Portraits, nd (Box 30, Folder 28029-28030)
    - Children, ca. 1920 (Box 30, Folder 28031)
    - John Lovejoy Elliott (Box 30, Folder 28032-28033)